Guide to the Conference on Law in Colonial Africa, Audiorecordings SC1283
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Conference on Law in Colonial Africa, Audiorecordings
1988 Apr 07-09
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Mann, Kristin, 1946-
SC1283
.5 Linear Feet (12 audiocassettes)
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Kristin Mann, 2016.
Law -- Africa; Mann, Kristin, 1946-
- Law in Colonial Africa, Thursday evening (1 of 2), 1988-04-07-09; 1.01 (Box 1, Audiocassette 1)
- Law in Colonial Africa, Thursday evening (2 of 2), 1988-04-07-09; 1.02 (Box 1, Audiocassette 2)
- Law in Colonial Africa, Friday morning (1 of 2), 1988-04-07-09; 1.03 (Box 1, Audiocassette 3)
- Law in Colonial Africa, Friday morning (2 of 2), 1988-04-07-09; 1.04 (Box 1, Audiocassette 4)
- Law in Colonial Africa, Friday afternoon (1 of 2), 1988-04-07-09; 1.05 (Box 1, Audiocassette 5)
- Law in Colonial Africa, Friday afternoon (2 of 2), 1988-04-07-09; 1.06 (Box 1, Audiocassette 6)
- Law in Colonial Africa, Saturday morning (1 of 2), 1988-04-07-09; 1.07 (Box 1, Audiocassette 7)
- Law in Colonial Africa, Saturday morning (2 of 2), 1988-04-07-09; 1.08 (Box 1, Audiocassette 8)
- Law in Colonial Africa, Saturday afternoon (1 of 2), 1988-04-07-09; 1.09 (Box 1, Audiocassette 9)
- Law in Colonial Africa, Saturday afternoon (2 of 2), 1988-04-07-09; 1.10 (Box 1, Audiocassette 10)
- Law in Colonial Africa, Reflections, #1, 1988-04-07-09; 1.11 (Box 1, Audiocassette 11)
- Law in Colonial Africa, Reflections #2, 1988-04-07-09; 1.12 (Box 1, Audiocassette 12)